Now I've taken weakness as my ally
I can fly to the highest heights
If I would just stop here
all I've lost would lose its luster
If you were lost out somewhere
at the same time my heart is shaken
I'd have no way to find you
your kindness, or even your strength
I know....
It's time for the dawn!
My peak performance
I'll blow straight past in a blast, yeah
You'll be left frozen with laughs
The days of pain left in the past, let's hope
As I make foes of the world
Im bracing myself upon shaking legs, yeah
Just keep me going for a few more steps
Now, this is the comeback, the time to awaken is now
Now, this is the comeback the time to awaken is now
Good to know you've still got
that cocky side to ya, Straw Hat!
When your mind and body catch up to your power,
that's when Awakening happens!
And your power's
just plain ridiculous...
I've already lost so much...
So much of the empire I built, gone!
My underlings, and the castle!
Same goes for you, don't it?
True, but I've got stuff
I gotta take back from ya!
Kundali Dragon Swarm!
Ya big dope!
Howzzat for ya!!
Every floor of the castle
below us is on fire.
Pretty sure thousands of
your soldiers are stuck there, too.
And they're all gonna
roast to death!
Don't sell 'em short, Kaido!
I trusted 'em to take care of everything
goin' on down there for me!
And I did that so I could...
...focus on kickin' your ass sky-high!
The way you laugh pisses me off!
Demolition Gust!
It's not just the castle anymore!
All the towers are burning!
Guyyyys!
Where'd everybody go?!
Where are you all?!
Heeeey!
Chopper!
Nami!
You all right?!
What do we do?!
We can't put out the fire!
Zoro, Sanji, Franky, Brook,
Usopp, Robin, and Jinbe...
I haven't found any of them!
They might be stuck in the fire!
Really?!
But...
Even if we went searching,
all of Onigashima's in flames!
Here isn't safe, either!
Unless the island lands,
we've got nowhere to go!
Zeus, can't you use your rain
to put out the fire?
In a fire like this?!
I'd be baked crispy!
We all worked so hard
to get this far!
How could it end like this?
Don't worry!
Huh?
It's all gonna be totally okay,
so no giving up!
We can't escape!
The fire's everywhere!
There's nowhere to run!
Dammit all!
I can't take it anymore!
I'm not made for this heat!
It's way too much work
to lug you around, Bepo!
Yeooow!
Maybe this is the end...
I don't think we can
get out of this one!
Save us, Captaaaain!
My precious afro is becoming
more curly by the moment!
That it is...
I'd prefer to not end up
looking like you, Brook.
Eh?
Huuuh?!
A skeleton!
I feel your frustration!
To be reduced to that state...
I don't know what to say!
My condolences to you...
You must have been slow in escaping
and burned to a crisp!
Come now,
I am no charred corpse!
I am dead though...
My goodness,
is the burning ever intense!
Perhaps there isn't a way
for all of us to escape, after all...
Perhaps not...
No go...
We can't escape from here
with the courtyard gone.
Oh, no!
The abyss to our front,
and hell's at our backs...
Can't even turn around
and head back, huh...
Nowhere to run
while we're midair...
The fire, the collapsing castle,
and the ladies...
Well, what to do then...
I don't wanna hear, "It's hot!"
Bust down the damn wall!
Unless you'd rather die here!
Just sacrifice one of your damn arms!
What use is that huge body
of yours anyway, dumbass?!
Wanna fight, do ya,
you moron?!
The heat and the flames
have put us in a pickle!
Is there a way for us to survive?!
If we had a clue,
this wouldn't be an issue!
The heat will kill us
if we can't find a solution!
Just keep running!
Please, do something, sir!
I'm gonna put out this fire, then!
Sure-Kill Green Star:
Sprinkler!
This is the very definition of
"a drop in the bucket," my good man!
Shaddap! I gotta figure something out!
I promised Izo, dammit!
Iwanna save Kin and Kiku...
and myself, too!
Hueh?!
Sir, please include me as well!
The castle's burnin' outta control!
Which way do we go?!
Zoro's hangin' by a thread!
Gotta get him to Chopper ASAP!
We're all gonna be cooked
before that happens!
So hot, so hot!
I just wanna survive!
Help us, Big Bro!
Who's whinin' back there?!
Don't make me
set ya on fire!
Please don't!
Another dead end! Dammit!
Flames and debris
keep getting in our way!
Did someone run around
setting these fires?!
Death by fire rather than by the hand of the enemy
is not the way I plan on going down in this raid!
Some fight this turned out to be...
We're not gonna let
some fire get us!
Yeah! We're making it through this!
Aye!
I am prepared, Jinbe-dono!
I am grateful for your trust in me!
Luffy chose to ally
with you and yours, Samurai!
What place has doubt here?
Come, do what you must!
I shall! If anything,
I am the one placing my trust in you!
Ever since that day,
I have been prepared...
Toki-sama!
Momonosuke-sama!
Hiyori-sama!
Make haste!
Haste, I say!
I could not defend Oden-sama that day...
I allowed Momonosuke-sama
and the others to suffer in that inferno of a castle!
Even with my Ninja Arts,
could not save anybody then!
A great blunder
for which I must repent!
I never, ever want...
...to feel that way again!
Tis Zou?!
Inuarashi, what manner of rain is this?!
Zunesha is bathing itself.
What an incredible amount of water!
May I partake?
will not permit those that
took part in this raid...
to die to these accursed flames!
I have kept you waiting
for too long, everyone!
I shall display water flowing in such ways
that will leave you in disbelief!
Ninja Art: Scrolling Technique!
The Elephant's Bath
-
Restoration!
Massive, indeed!
Water Heart,
Fishman Jujutsu:
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
Fill every last bit of this castle!
Be enough, waters of Zou,
to rescue us all!
Let me down, guys!
You gotta let us do
somethin' for ya, Killer-san!
Wow, hot!
What do we do now?!
There's actually nowhere else to run!
What's that?!
That's one hell of a rumble...
Water?!
We're saved!
Make haste, Momonosuke-kun!
Why must I?! Kaido yet lives!
You must keep this island afloat
with your Flame Clouds!
I, keep the island afloat?!
An impossible task!
Kaido is surely close to his limits!
His Flame Clouds will not
last much longer!
Heh?
You must create Flame Clouds
to keep Onigashima in the skies!
Ehhhh?!
This was our only option
from the very start!
As things stand,
Onigashima will plummet to the surface!
You can do it, Momonosuke-kun!
Create Flame Clouds!
Momonosuke-kun!
Just out with the Flame Clouds!
'Tis easier said than done...
I cannot do it!
They will not come out!
Momonosuke
Go with Kin'emon
and the others.
You are to leap
twenty years into the future,
and return the Kozuki Clan
to greatness!
I cannot do it!
Then why will you and Hiyori
not come with us?!
Momonosuke-sama!
Your mother's suffering is
greater than yours!
This is the land of samurai,
where shame alone could end your life!
For a man to complain
after a woman has set her resolve...
...is mortal shame!
I am but a child...!
With all due respect,
as Oden-sama is no longer with us,
you are no longer an ordinary child!
You are the son of a great samurai!
And one day, you will lead our country!
If you would allow me to be so forward...!
Will you permit us
one more chance to fight?!
If I am going to burn to death regardless,
then I would die wielding my blade
in the name of my lord!
Prithee would you give us
the chance to die as samurai?!
Momonosuke!
Mother...
I shall go!
Aye...
However you can, live...!
I am too ashamed to face Mother!
I am no longer some ordinary child!
I am the man that will be
Shogun of this land!
Mm!
I will save our country!
Halt, Onigashima!
Wait, not that way!
Not that way!
Not toward the capital!
Gum-Gum...
Lightning!
You're tellin' me you can grab lightning?!
Whatta load of bull!
Wha?!
Seriously, his power is bull...
Gum-Gum
Why, ya little jerk!
You can play around...
Huh?
...all you want!
But...
A Devil Fruit power
will never conquer the world!
Amazing, how things work.
Just like how Roger
never ate a Devil Fruit...
Only Haki...
...can transcend all!
Destroyer of Death...
...Thunder...
...Bagua!
We send to those
that have passed on...
Set sail!
Release your sky lantern boats!
Steady as she goes!
The festival's end draws near...
Tomorrow, we return to
laboring as slaves...
I hope I can live to see another year...
Steady as she goes!
Reach my Daddy!
What the?!
The hell're you tryin'
to do to me?!
Dammit, leggo!
All you're doin' is
giving away your location!
Dragon Twister...
Demolition Breath!
Bet you're still wide open to
cutting attacks!
Get down here,
Straw Hat!
Hey, it came out!
Some kind of tremor
pulled the Sea Prism Stone nail out!
Damn you...
At least I can take you down with me!
Are you watching, Oden?!
Your daughter...
...dies with me!
Kingpin Hyogoro!
I heard Onigashima's plummeting!
That means he's cornered Kaido...
Tell me, men!
Which would you rather?
If the Straw Hat Man takes Kaido down,
we fall, and we die.
If we survive,
it means Kaido wins!
Come on, the choice is simple!
I have a kid in Hakumai.
I have a wife in Ringo!
If Kaido goes down,
our families live happily ever after!
Wouldn't that be something?
Hell of a country ours would be then!
Have you damn samurai lost your minds?!
That'd mean you all die!
That's just as well, isn't it?
Straw Hat-san!
Beat Kaido back to where he belongs!
I don't wanna die!
Ow, hot, ow!
don't wanna diffie!
I'm gonna survive no matter what!
You're the best!
Water?!
Kiku, Kin'emon!
I'm not gonna give up!
Halt, Onigashima!
Heeey! Momo!
I'm finishing this, right here!
Onigashima's in my way!
Move it!
Incredible...
It is as if he intends to punch
straight through Onigashima...
Stop!
Uwhoh!
Wait, Luffy!
I still cannot...!
Momo!
I trust ya!
OUTWITTED
"Time's up"
Someone said again, with a laugh
Fine then, hide-and-seek playtime...
...is over
Let's go, come on (We can see it soon)
Let your heart beat out
and things will change (We can see it soon)
Grow strong, you have time
Lift up that dream
The overflowing loneliness can't sustain me alone
We were so free in our younger days
What a dumb dream
...to live
Shining a light on uncharted ways
Get on our feet and try
Let's see the ends of the world together
Together, we can go and fly